I have been programming since 8th grade and have worked on a variety of different projects. I've reverse engineered kernel byte code, implemented network protocols, created deep learning models, and done full stack web development. I love learning about programming and computers so I can build new and exciting things.

585-465-3716 axs9701@rit.edu

742 Wayneport RD Macedon NY 14502

GPA: 3.61

Languages

- [5] C#
- [4] PHP
- [4] C++
- [4] Python
- [3] Javascript
- [3] Scala
- [2] SQL
- [2] HTML
- [2] CSS

Software

- Linux
- git
- Docker
- Postgres
- Jenkins

Notable Classes Taken

- Algorithms
- OOP Design
- Web Security
- Deep Learning
- Embedded Systems
- Intro to Big Data
- Stellar Astrophysics

Education

RIT — Masters in Computer Science, Bachelors in Software Engineering,
Minor in Computer Security
Graduating May 2020

Work Experience

Datto, Software Engineer Intern — May 2019 - Aug 2019

The product my team maintained backs up GSuite and O365 data which consisted of a Scala, PHP, and Ruby backend with a basic web interface using bootstrap. I worked on adding new features into the application as well as fixing issues that were directly affecting customer backups. I also worked with my hackathon team to build a raspberry pi device to create new JIRA tickets when snack bins are empty.

EagleView, Software Engineer Co-Op — Jan 2018 - Aug 2018

I worked with a scrum team doing full stack web development for both customer facing applications and internal micro-services. I worked with Postgres databases, a PHP backend, a JS frontend, and HTML/CSS. I also started a micro-service in Go for my team, laying the foundation for future development and deployment.

RSA, Software Engineer Co-Op — Jan 2017 - Aug 2017

I worked on desktop printer coordination software with a small team. I implemented printer network protocols after using Wireshark for analysis and integrated this into existing software. I also developed a much better algorithm to remove hole punch marks from scanned documents using a deep learning model that I trained.

Personal Projects

Garbage Full Detector - https://github.com/Experiment5X/GarbageFullDetector

A deep learning classifier that runs on a raspberry pi with a camera to detect if my garbage is full and notify people when it hasn't been taken out.

Feature Map Viewer - https://github.com/Experiment5X/DeepFeatureVisualizationWebApp An application for generating visualizations of feature maps in the CNN VGG-16.

Velocity - https://github.com/hetelek/Velocity

A cross-platform desktop application for managing proprietary Xbox360 files, and bypassing security measures with over 150,000 downloads.

ClaptchaSolver - https://github.com/Experiment5X/ClaptchaSolver A neural network that breaks CAPTCHAs with ~45% accuracy.